# Pasqualino Sorice

## Computer Engineer

Via di Valle Schioia 178, 00042, Anzio (RM), Lazio Π

✓ https://pasqualinosorice.com
 ✓ linosorice@gmail.com
 □ +39 388 3645 185
 ✓ linosorice
 f linosorice
 f linosorice
 f linosorice
 f linosorice
 f linosorice

Pasqualino Sorice is a computer engineer specialized in Android (Java) and iOS (Swift) apps development and lately he is working with React Native. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including Swift, Java, JavaScript, SQL, and Python. Strong background in project management and customer relations. He is a fast learner, and flexible worker and he always gets updated on the last news about development. He is currently in a remote team called BuildTeam that works on a STEEM blockchain. Employed for the last 3 years for a startup called Promo Inside where he sharpened his technical skills on mobile development Android and iOS and where he builds a product called AppMobileRental. He also started a company called Hubern that provides IT consulting.

## SKILLS -

Mobile Apps  Master			Frontend Advanced				Backend Advanced			
react nati	ve ios	android	bootstrap	css	html	jquery	node.js	mon	godb	sql
java sv	vift		javascript	react			python	php	ruby	
Frameworks			Server Administration				Other			
Advanced			Intermediate				Intermediate			
express	sails	ruby on rails	apache	nginx	mysql		c ans	ible	git sv	n bash
django	laravel	gatsbyjs	nagios i	ptables	3					

#### WORK EXPERIENCE (6)

Founder at Gopaybot September 2017- Current https://gopaybot.com

Founder at QuizInCloud March 2017- Current http://quizincloud.com

CEO/President at Hubern S.r.l.s. July 2016- October 2017

https://hubern.com

Mobile App Director at Promo Inside S.r.l.s. October 2014- October 2017 http://promoinside.com

Software Engineer at VividaWeb March 2015- July 2015 http://www.vividaweb.it/

Android Developer at Innovandia S.r.l. March 2014- August 2014

#### VOLUNTEER

IT guy at La coccinella
July 2013 - October 2016
http://www.cooplacoccinella.org/

An onlus engaged in projects for the benefit of children and families in difficulty.

#### EDUCATION (2) -

Master of Science in Engineering in Computer Science at Università degli Studi di Roma La Sapienza 2013 - 2016

**Grade:** 110/110

Bachelor of Science in Engineering in Computer Science and Control Engineering at Università degli Studi di Roma La Sapienza

2009 - 2012 **Grade:** 102/100

#### LANGUAGES

Italian English
Native Speaker Fluent

### INTERESTS

portrait landscape

Photography Guitar

rock hard rock metal